Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
James A. Roberts papers
1971-2000
SC0626
Roberts, James A.
225 Linear feet
Papers pertain to his work as an environmental engineer in the United States and abroad and include reports, impact statements, proposals, correspondence, memoranda, contracts, financial records, publications, maps, and plans. Collection also includes Environmental Case Law materials and course materials from classes Roberts taught. Some papers pertain to associations he worked with such as Global Environmental Management Services, Global Environmental Institute, and the National Association of Environmental Professionals.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
James A. Roberts earned his AB in geography at Stanford in 1955.
Description of the Collection
Papers pertain to his work as an environmental engineer in the United States and abroad and include reports, impact statements, proposals, correspondence, memoranda, contracts, financial records, publications, maps, and plans. Collection also includes Environmental Case Law materials and course materials from classes Roberts taught. Some papers pertain to associations he worked with such as Global Environmental Management Services, Global Environmental Institute, and the National Association of Environmental Professionals.
Access Terms
Global Environmental Institute.; Global Environmental Management Services.; National Association of Environmental Professionals.; Roberts, James A.; Environmental impact analysis.; Environmental sciences.
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - UTR (Upper Truckee River & Wetlands Restoration Project) Phase I Report Vol. I-IV 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Roberts, Que Es lo Ques Es in RIA? (Global Environmental Management Services) 4 copies (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - EIR (Environmental Impact Report) examples: Wetland Delineation Report 1992; Minerals Management Plan, Nevada City 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - USDA Forest Service Tahoe publications 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - California Planners Book of Lists 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - EIR examples: Tahoe Summit 1997; American Canyon Incorporation 1992; Streambank Protection for the Lower American River 1997; Council on Environmental Quality 1993; Roblar Rd. Quarry 1986; American River Bridge Crossing Record of Decision 1996; Cache Creek Preliminary User Plan 1985; Texas Risk Reduction v.1-3 1996; State Water Resources Control Board (SWRCB) 1994; Mojave Desert Tortoise USDI F&W Service 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EPA Principles of Environmental Enforcement 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EIR examples: Urban Land Institute- State of California 1995; Environmental Yellow Pages- Central Florida 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - UTR miscellaneous reports, articles, publications (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - EIR examples: CQI Battle for Natural Resources 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publications, pamphlets, brochures (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - EIR examples: Forest Service Decision-Making 1997; Economic Redevelopment Forecast 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NEPA/CEQA (National Environmental Policy Act/California Environmental Quality Act): CEQA Guidelines, Revisions (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NEPA/CEQA: Morgan, Lewis, & Bockius (law firm) publications (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NEPA/CEQA: CEQA case law binder (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NEPA/CEQA: CEQA workshop materials 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NEPA/CEQA: California State publications- permits, planning 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NEPA/CEQA: NEPA U.S. Air Force Federal Environmental Quality Awards (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NEPA/CEQA: Environmental Impact Assessment 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NEPA/CEQA: California Energy Commission- Fuels 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NEPA/CEQA: Florida Environmental Equity & Justice Commission Report 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NEPA/CEQA: California County reports, memoranda 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NEPA/CEQA: Guide to CEQA, 1992 ed. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CEQA memoranda, presentation handouts, articles 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NEPA/CEQA: Land Use & Law miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NEPA/CEQA California planning: Bay Area Clean Air Plan 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: California Permit Handbook 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: California Planners Book of Lists 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: California Statistical Abstract 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: California Land Use & Planning Law 1994 ed. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: law & legislation correspondence, memoranda 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: legislation (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Laurel Heights v. UCSF memorandum 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Goleta v. Santa Barbara County BOS 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Concerned Citizens v. Costa Mesa 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Planning- State & County publications (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: CEQA proposed legislation 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: CEQA update 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Roberts article “course pack” 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: guidelines, updates, reprints 1978-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: EIR guidelines, drafts, related publications 1973-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NEPA/CEQA, CA: Journal of Environmental Law & Litigation vol. 7 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Summit Lake and Silver Spring (SL/SS) A/P: photographs & slides 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SL/SS: initial analysis report and draft 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SL/SS: notes, maps (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - SL/SS: correspondence, memoranda, notes, maps (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SL/SS: environmental report (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - SL/SS: memoranda, correspondence, notes (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - SL/SS: slides (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SL/SS: airport Master Plan/ Environmental Assessment 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - SL/SS: airport Master Plan draft 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lumos & Associates: correspondence, memoranda re: Merger 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Lumos: Employee Handbook 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lumos: Sacramento Interests (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lumos: correspondence Paul Lemos, Buzz Fitzpatrick etc. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lumos: Pinenut Estates correspondence 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lumos: Sacramento area marketing & planning (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lumos: marketing team (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Lumos: Reno River Restoration Project (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lumos: miscellaneous maps, forms, resumes, newsletters (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Lumos: management meetings (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Lumos: GEMS information packet 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Lumos: management meetings (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Lumos: Sacramento Riverfront Improvements 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Cook Islands: Prime Minister 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Cook Islands: Proposal for EA 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cook Islands: Aitutaki Island (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cook Islands: Iceland: Manganese/Geotherm (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cook Islands: proposal draft & correspondence from minister (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cook Islands: Aitutaki P-95011 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cook Islands: 02994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cook Islands: pamphlets, newspapers (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cook Islands: Roberts Infrastructure Plan 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cook Islands: Roberts Rarotonga Integrated Infrastructure Plan 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cook Islands: State of Environment Report draft (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cook Islands: Rarotonga Outline Scheme for Water Development & Management 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cook Islands: miscellaneous articles, reports, brochures (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cook Islands: first draft report (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cook Islands: Taro (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cook Islands: Asian Development Bank proposal 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cook Islands: Norwegian Aluminum Industry- Emissions Report 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Conservation, Endangered Species periodicals, reports, flyers, newsletters, pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Carrying Capacity Network conference materials, etc. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Energy miscellaneous publications 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - miscellaneous periodicals, catalogs 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - AEP (Association of Environmental Professionals) 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - EIR/EIS examples: California, Asia 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Primer on Environmental Law in California 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - CEQA Legal Glossary 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - California Office of Planning & Research Economic Practices Manual 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - CEQA 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- D (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- E (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- F (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- G (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- H (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- I (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Case Law decisions- J (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NPS & Brazil Training: Manual, Policy & Procedures for HSB ISO 14000/Walker masters thesis 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NPS & Brazil Training: Mechanisms to Implement Environmental Law training program, Brazil 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NPS & Brazil Training: Tools for Protecting Parks Course Manual 9/1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NPS & Brazil Training: Tools for Protecting Parks Course Manual 11/1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NPS & Brazil Training: Tools for Protecting Parks Course Manual 5/1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 05393 UTR Correspondence #2: Phase 1 Report & Appendices vol. 1 & related 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 05393.01.700 Deliverables (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 05393 Phase 1 Report, Master 7/1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05393 Report drafts & related (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 05393.01.700a EIR (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 05393.02 Phase 2 file log (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 05393.02.100a MIG-PIOP (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 05393.02.100d ERA subcontract (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 05393.02.100h G&S subcontract (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 05393.02.100c FG subcontract (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 05393.02.100f ES subcontract (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 05393.02.100e LA subcontract (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 05393.02.100b QA/QC subcontract (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 05393.02.300 notes to file (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 05393 meeting 5/8/1996 8 mini-cassettes (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 05393 meeting 12/18/1995 5 mini-cassettes (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 05393.02.400f ES in (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 05393.02.400h Gibson & Skordal (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 05393.02.400b QA/QC in (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 05393.02.400c FG in (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 05393.02.400e LA in (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 05393.02.400d ER/GIS in (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 05393.02.500 Global out (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 05393 2nd round reports: Budget Control Book (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 05393 CTC & OPMD Comments on Preliminary Draft Conceptual Design Report 1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 05393 Edited copy, edits through 12/18/1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 05393 Hydrogeomorphic Classification for Wetlands reprints (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 05393 memoranda, commentary & responses (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 95019 EDCWA (El Dorado County Water Agency) Water Program & El Dorado Project EIR 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 95019.1 publications (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 95019.2 2nd review (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 95019.2 Suppl. EIR 3rd Review (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 95019.2 Suppl. EIR Background Notes (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 95019.2 Suppl. EIR pages to insert (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 95019.3 Final EIR general (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 95019.3 Suppl. EIR draft 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 95019.3 comments & correspondence (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 95019.3 FEIR master comments (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 95019.2 EDCWA: Suppl. EIR 1st review (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 95019.3 miscellaneous drafts, comments (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 95022 Slovakia CCC 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 97021 Australia: Docklands project 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 97023 Australia: Department of Infrastructure Victoria (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 97022 Australia: DNRE, Victoria (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Australia publications (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Australia: Docklands reports, etc. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Australia: publications- travel brochures, maps, guides (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1997-98 Projects: memorabilia (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous reports, correspondence 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Timberline 1980 #4 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Timberline Report master (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - China Trip report on teaching 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Master trip report Philippines & Thailand 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Timberline EIR analysis & draft responses (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - GRIPS (Geothermal Resource Impact Projection Study) Plan & Bibliography 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - China Trip 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - UCD-EPC #2 Hell-Hole draft 1976-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Zhijin Wu proposal 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Jara Corp. mailing list (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Asia Foundation – Philippines follow-up 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Asia Foundation – Philippines follow-up 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - EIR handbook material: Acta Environmentalica Universitatis Comenianae vols. 4-5 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - EIR handbook material: Szego, Human Cartography (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - EIR handbook material: Barron & Cottrell, eds., Making Environmental Law in Asia More Effective (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - EIR handbook material: Lal, ed., Soil Erosion Research Methods (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - EIR handbook material: Roberts, Just What Is ER? (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - EIR handbook material: Roberts, Que es lo Que Que es in RIA? (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - EIR handbook material: McElfish Jr. & Beir, Environmental Regulation of Coal Mining (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - EIR handbook material: Roberts, MKB-vadardet? (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - EIR handbook material: MKB publications- Sweden (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - EIR handbook material: Egypt-Zaire Power system Connectivity Study Vol. 1&2 draft 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - EIR handbook material: Environmental Law Developments Seminar 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - EIR handbook material: Chelshire Downs/Granite Bay Addendum to EIR final draft 1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - EIR handbook material: Australia: miscellaneous publications (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous articles 1980s (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - SRI Environmental Challenges to Business 1986 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, Population Projections, Power Plants, CEQA publications, correspondence 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NEPA plan 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Land Use, Litigation publications 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Waste Management, CEQA Case Glossary, Planning, Geography, Water, Development publications (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan: correspondence 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan: EIR class, notes, map, brochures (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Taiwan: Roberts facsimiles (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Taiwan publications (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan: Kaohsiung Metro Park proposals, reports- EIR/CEQA/NEPA examples (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan: Report on P&D Projects for Construction & Planning Administration Phase I, III, Final draft 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan: Report figures, appendices, etc. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan: Roberts, “The Changing Pacific” (St. Marks United Methodist Church) articles from China Post 10-11/1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan: newspapers, articles (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - EIS coursework: Habitat Conservation Planning Handbook USF&WS 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - EIS coursework: IRWA Course 601 Student workbook, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - EIS coursework: IRWA Course 600 Instructor’s Manual 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - EIS coursework: IRWA Course 601 Instructor’s Manual 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - EIS coursework: Roberts, Environmental Planning, Impact Evaluation, & Reporting (presentation materials) 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - EIS coursework: Environmental Policy Development & Implementation vol. II training program (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - EIS coursework: International Roundtable on EIA & Public Participation in Environmental Decision-Making- Wroclaw, Poland 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mather Field Wetlands – Mather Airforce Base: cleanup reports (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mather: Economic Development Agency Grant Roadway Improvements 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Mather: Specific Plan 2/1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mather: Specific Plan 9/1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Mather: Specific Plan draft 3/1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Mather: related material- photographs, comparable plans (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Mather: Contaminated Property Cleanup Guide (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mather: Site Characteristics Report 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GEI (Global Environmental Institute) II: File Index (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - GEI II: Centre for Environmental Management & Planning 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - GEI II: Sacramento Council for International Visitors (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - GEI II: Western Partnership for Environmental Technology Education (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GEI II: Environmental Law Institute (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - GEI II: New Europe Institute (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - GEI II: U.S. Environmental Training Institute (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - GEI II: Participant Training Project for Europe (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - GEI II: National Environmental Training Center for Smaller Communities (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - GEI II: Asia Foundation Environmental Fellowship Program (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - GEI II: Academy for Educational Development 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - GEI II: Euro Commission (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - GEI II: National Bureau of Purchasing Management (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - GEI II: Lang & Associates: Healthy by Design 1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - GEI II: National Association of State Revenue Agencies (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - GEI II: Fundraising (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - GEI II: Funding (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - GEI II: African Development Bank (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - GEI II: Asian Development Bank (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - GEI II: World Bank (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - GEI II: US AID Asia Partnership (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - GEI II: US AID (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - GEI II: European Bank (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - GEI II: InterAmerican Development Bank 1995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - GEI II: Data on Consultants DACON (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - GEI II: US EPA (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - GEI II: Environmental Partnership for Central Europe (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - GEI II: National Academy of Sciences (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - GEI II: Asia Foundation (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - GEI II: Eurasia Foundation (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - GEI II: Internal Programs Consortium (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - GEI II: ISAR (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - GEI II: PRAGMA Corp. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - GEI II: NASDA Grants to Asian Markets (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - GEI II: U.S. Baltic Foundation (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - GEI II: NBD (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - GEI II: U.S. Slovak Science & Technology Fund (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - GEI II: NBD: German Marshall Fund (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - GEI II: NBD: USETI (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - GEI II: U.S. EPA Funding Assistance (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - GEI II: U.S. Trade & Development Agency (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - GEI II: UNCED (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - GEI II: NBD: U.N. Environmental Programme (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - GEI II: ISAR-INCEIA Institute 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - GEI II: RHAA GEMS (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - GEI II: miscellaneous sales brochures (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Roberts course materials: ECI-EIA course 1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Roberts course materials: miscellaneous 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Roberts course materials: EIR papers 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Roberts course materials: miscellaneous reports, memoranda, brochures (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Roberts course materials: Roberts, Environmental Monitoring 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Roberts course materials: Biographies of Selected American Naturalists (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Roberts course materials: Biographies- student work (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Roberts course materials: Biographies- master 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Roberts course materials: teaching possibilities 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Roberts course materials: UCD course, EMCON 1993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Roberts course materials: ‘The Environment is Your Responsibility Too’ St. Mark’s Women’s Club 1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Roberts course materials: Renaissance society “Dinosaurs & The Environmental Ethic” 1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Roberts course materials: “The Environmental Ethic” 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Roberts course materials: CEEF: Science Fair Talk 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Roberts course materials: Anna Radnai visit 1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Roberts course materials: Environmental Justice- racism articles (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - EIR handbooks: Environmental Deskbook 1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - EIR handbooks: Council on Environmental Quality- Considering Cumulative Effects under NEPA (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - EIR handbooks: Intellectual Property (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - EIR handbooks: Sonoma County CEQA Audit (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - EIR handbooks: Roberts, Environmental Planning & Management (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - EIR handbooks: Proposal: Consultant Services to Evaluate the Scenic Quality of Eligible Scenic Highways” California 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - EIR handbooks: Environmental Analysis & Reporting for Transportation Plans 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SWRCB (State Water Resources Control Board) publications: Bay/Delta Control Plan (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SWRCB: Toxic Waste 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - SWRCB: Instream Water Uses (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SWRCB: Waste (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - UTR accounting: CTC 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - UTR accounting: Interflure (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - UTR accounting: Toby Haynes 1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - UTR accounting: 05393 A/R #3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - UTR accounting: 05393 A/R #2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - UTR accounting: 05393 A/R #1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - UTR accounting: 05393 A/R #4 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - UTR accounting: invoices (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - UTR accounting: invoice working file (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - UTR accounting: 05393.02.203 Team Member Cost Scoping (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - UTR accounting: notes to file on critical needs & payments (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - GEMS taxes: supplemental information 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - GEMS taxes: 1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - GEMS taxes: Global Partnership (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - GEMS taxes: Partnership returns 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - GEMS taxes: State forms 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - GEMS taxes: Small Business Backup Information (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - GEMS taxes: returns 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - GEMS taxes: Partnership 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - GEMS taxes: Cash Receipts 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - GEMS taxes: Cash Receipts 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - GEMS taxes: Cash Receipts 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - GEMS taxes: Cash Receipts 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - GEMS taxes: W-45 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - GEMS taxes: 1099s 1991 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - GEMS taxes: Wells Fargo Market Rate Account (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - GEMS taxes: information 1996 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - GEMS taxes: 1099s, W2s 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - GEMS taxes: Payroll (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - GEMS taxes: Reconciled Bank statements (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - GEMS taxes: Line of Credit (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - GEMS taxes: Payroll (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - GEMS taxes: Calculation (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - GEMS taxes: Rent (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - GEMS taxes: Fed. Forms (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - GEMS taxes: 8736 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 18)